{
    "subject": "resource/The_Man_Behind_the_Gun",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/Felix_Feist",
    "human_readable": "The director of 'The Man Behind the Gun' is Felix Feist.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8914968967437744,
            "question": "Is Felix Feist a film director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8819078803062439,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Felix Feist."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8715295791625977,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Man Behind the Gun'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8382277488708496,
            "question": "What film is Felix Feist known for directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8372912406921387,
            "question": "Who was responsible for directing 'The Man Behind the Gun'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8350540995597839,
            "question": "Felix Feist directed which movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8250043392181396,
            "question": "What is the name of the director of 'The Man Behind the Gun'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8203724026679993,
            "question": "What is the name of the director associated with 'The Man Behind the Gun'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8073475360870361,
            "question": "Which director helmed the film 'The Man Behind the Gun'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.569667637348175,
            "question": "Felix Feist worked in what profession?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of 'The Man Behind the Gun' is Felix Feist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2952_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which director helmed the film 'The Man Behind the Gun'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2952_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the director associated with 'The Man Behind the Gun'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2952_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the director of 'The Man Behind the Gun'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2952_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2952_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. Specifically, document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2952/re-ranker-msmarco/36.txt` and `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2952/re-ranker-msmarco/46.txt` both mention Felix Feist as the director of 'The Man Behind the Gun' (1953)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Felix E. Feist, including his role as a director for \"The Man Behind the Gun\" (1953). Therefore, the statement that Felix Feist directed \"The Man Behind the Gun\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}